If there's one thing I hear patients say
even more than "save my life,"
it's this...
"I want to go home."
It's weird spending all of your time
in a place that most people hate.
_
You're back.
Hey. You're back.
Are you still drunk?
No.
Are you nervous?
No. Are you?
I was, but I snuck in
and did two lap choles
before breakfast, so...
_
- Welcome back.
- Hey.
Have either one of you seen
a package at the house?
What package?
Well, Cristina was sending something...
you know, "Congratulations
on not becoming a drifter
slash getting dumped
by a resident" present...
but I don't know where it is.
Ooh. Maybe it's a stripper.
What is wrong with you?
Sorry. Hormones.
Well, knowing her, it's a cadaver.
But this hospital, in particular...
Welcome back, Dr. Grey!
...it's where I grew up.
It's where my fondest memories happened.
This is the best day of my life.
Mine, too, Helm.
Bailey re-hired you?
Well, I was gonna tell you,
but you were too busy dumping me.
I did not dump you.
I asked you to take some time.
Rob/steal. Murder/kill.
It all means the same thing.
It's home.
Thanks.
Get your residents together.
Time for rounds.
Even if it's a broken home.
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
Wendy Bliss to Urology.
You still need to eat.
How you holding up?
I'm still standing.
You talk to Maggie?
Gemma.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I have to ask.
Just be easy on her, okay?
Who was that?
A friend.
Hi.
I'm looking for Chief Karev.
Uh, Karev's on a personal day.
Can I help you?
I'm Dr. Daphne Lopez.
I'm here for a walk-through.
Oh, oh. Right, right. Yeah.
Karev said that you were coming.
You're the ER doc from UCLA?
Yep. That's me.
- Well, and good to finally meet you.
- Yeah.
I'm Owen Hunt, and this is
Dr. Richard Webber.
- Pleasure.
- Nice to meet you.
Um, Karev said that
we're trying to woo you
to see if we can get you
to come over here
instead of Seattle Pres.
Well, I'll tell you a secret...
you're winning.
They can't afford me.
You really should start
bringing all your patients
here, you know?
Oh, yeah? "Sorry, sir.
I know you're having
a heart attack right now,
but my dude works across town
at Grey-Sloan, so..."
- Yeah.
- "...we got to go."
- He'll understand.
- Yeah?
- What time does your shift end tonight?
- Tomorrow morning.
Well, maybe I'll show up
at the fire station
- with an emergency.
- Jackson.
And then I'll be
at the hospital across town.
Hey, Ma.
Mom, I did not know
you were back in town.
New ride?
Well, apparently limos
can be death traps.
Oh, yeah. I've seen them take
out entire wedding parties.
And, uh, this is...?
I'm... I'm Victoria Hughes, ma'am.
Station 19.
Station 19? What is that?
A TV channel?
No, ma'am. It's a... It's a fire station.
Mm.
Well, I...
- Yeah.
- I'm gonna... I'm gonna go.
- Mm.
- Sorry.
Sorry.
You lean into all paramedics like that?
Huh.
I like the hormones.
Hormones are good.
You're better.
- You have rounds.
- Oh, I can't.
I don't want to. Ah, just go.
Face them. I'll reward you later.
They are so mean.
I want my reward now.
No. Go.
- Levi, be great, okay?
- Oh.
Go prove them wrong.
Okay. I'll play.
I hope our baby has...
your eyes and my nose.
I hope our baby has
my hair and your brain.
Ooh. I don't know.
I'm not sure I want
this amygdala in our baby.
Maybe my basal ganglia?
Jo, do you think
that our baby should have
my prefrontal cortex or Link's?
What?
Are you okay?
Yeah. I, uh...
I signed up to be a Safe Haven volunteer,
which means that, when a baby
is dropped off at a fire station
in the vicinity, they call me, and...
they just called me.
- Whoa.
- Shepherd.
Dr. Brooks to Oncology.
How's your resting heart rate?
Oh. Um...
up 15%.
- Is that weird?
- No. Normal.
- Blood pressure?
- Down.
Ooh, this is fun.
It's like we're in a club.
See you.
Which therapist told you to do this?
Carly. But she...
she didn't tell me to do it.
She told me that she did it.
And how is that helpful?
Well, hearing her story
made me feel better...
and I don't know...
it just sounded nice... helping someone.
You sure it's not too much too soon?
Can you come with me?
Alex went to Iowa to help his mom.
I have a surgery.
Ugh.
I can cancel?
No. No. No. It's... I'm... It's good.
Are you sure?
Yeah. No. I'm fine.
Ooh, cake.
None for you, traitor.
I didn't mean to rat out Grey,
and you all know that.
I was just doing my job.
Mm-hmm. That's what the Nazis said.
Okay, my great-grandfather
was in a concentration camp,
so that's really not cool to say.
Apologize to the traitor.
Sorry, traitor.
Excuse me. Coming through.
Excuse me.
Look, Grey's back, all right?
So you can all shut up about it now.
- Hi, Elliott. Finley?
- Hi.
Wheelchair? What happened?
- Jasper happened.
- Jasper.
4 pounds, 14 ounces.
Wow. You had the baby!
I thought he wasn't due
for another month.
- Oh, he wasn't.
- No, but he's okay.
- He's in the NICU.
- Yeah.
Oh, yeah, show her, show her.
Check out this little alien.
Aww.
- Yeah.
- Isn't he cute?
We're calling him "E.T." for short.
Yeah, I was in the middle
of my usual pre-surgery fast
when her water broke.
He wanted to postpone,
and I was like, "No.
You don't postpone heart surgery."
Yeah. Jasper's immune system's
still a little wonky.
They're not letting me hold him
until I get discharged.
Schmitt, present, please.
Elliott Calhoun, 39,
here for a fourth
aortic valve replacement
due to congenital aortic stenosis.
Okay, 64-year-old male.
In remission for over a year
after being treated for mesothelioma.
Primary complaints
are night sweats, weight loss,
and an inguinal and testicular mass.
Lymphoma.
It's a little early to jump
to that conclusion, Simms.
Pretty solid conclusion to jump to.
Uh, you all
can go on to the next patient.
I've got this.
Dr. Bailey.
Captain Herrera.
I'm so sorry to see you back here.
Please don't tell your husband
my cancer's back.
Okay, first, we don't know that,
and of course I won't say a word.
Good morning, good morning.
- Good morning. Hi.
- Hi.
- Hi. Good morning.
Dr. DeLuca.
- Jamie Caldwell... 13.
- Jamie.
I know Jamie. I took out your
gallbladder two years ago.
How are we doing?
Zachary just commented on Tessa's photo
with a heart emoji. When I'm dying.
You're not dying. She's not dying. Right?
Jamie presents with a palpable
3 by centimeter mass
in between her ribs
on her right side, which...
- Hurts like hell.
- Yeah.
Language.
Can you cut this thing off
before Tessa's bat mitzvah?
Zachary Schultz isn't gonna
dance with a hunchback.
Who's presenting?
There a problem?
W-We already started.
Hi. Who are you?
Cormac Hayes, chief of pediatric surgery.
Since when?
Since this morning.
For the future,
let's not round on my patients
when I'm not here.
Start again.
Jamie Caldwell, 13,
presents with persistent back pain...
Hey, Alex. I'm at the fire station.
I'll explain later, but call me.
And say "hi" to your mom.
Bye.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Um... there was a-a baby
dropped off here?
Oh. Yeah, okay.
So, uh, if you change your mind,
according to law, you have 72 hours to...
Oh. Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
No. I'm not the mother.
I'm the Safe Haven thingy.
I'm sorry. So sorry. I'm Victoria Hughes.
Thanks for coming.
Oh, yeah, Vic.
Um, you're Jackson's girlfriend.
Girlf... Girlfriend?
Well, no. No labels.
But, um, did he say something?
Did... You know what? Never mind.
Um, sorry. Who are you?
- I...
- Uh, that would be Jo Karev.
Hi.
- Hey.
- Hi. Oh, wow.
- Oh.
That's a brand-new baby.
Yep. Fresh out the oven.
We're guessing three days old.
Engine requested to 368 Great Marsh Road.
That would be Mrs. Wiinikainen again.
What else does she have to burn down?
Um, Mrs. Wiinikainen
tends to light things on fire
when she gets lonely.
- Oof. Dark.
- Come on, guys. We got a call.
- Yeah.
- Let's go.
Oh, my goodness.
Come on. Let me show you around.
Okay.
So, I have a valve replacement
on a chronic aortic stenosis.
You want to scrub in?
Okay.
- Why?
- Hmm?
Why do you need me to scrub in
on a valve replacement?
No, I don't. I don't. I just...
thought it would be fun.
Okay, but it's a valve replacement,
which I'm pretty sure you can do
with your eyes closed.
Okay, well, if you don't want to help...
No. I do. I do.
God, I haven't seen a heart that
isn't traumatized in months.
- Too real.
- Okay.
It feels hard... almost like a bone.
Have we ordered a CT?
I was about to,
but then I got interrupted.
Jamie, I'm gonna get some scans
so we can get a better idea
of what's causing your pain
- and the, um...
- Zit-hump?
Right. That.
Okay, Parker. Let's get her up to CT.
Like I said.
Happy first day.
- Thank you.
We'll see you soon, Jamie.
Oh, how's the baby?
How are you feeling?
Oh, we're both good.
But she's acting up today, though.
Oh. She?
Just a hunch.
Uh, I'll find out for sure later today.
- Okay, you ready?
- No.
Fine.
Okay.
Oh.
That's a mass, isn't it?
We won't know if it's malignant
until we get a biopsy,
so let's not write any letters home yet.
With my history,
with the statistics
about firefighters and cancer?
No offense, but it doesn't
take a medical degree
to put that together.
No, but it does take a medical degree
to rule out all options before panicking.
So, I am going to get a biopsy.
We'll go from there, okay?
So?
Guess that caught you by surprise.
My son sneaking around with
another woman in plain sight?
What? No. Nobody's sneaking, okay?
I... broke up with Maggie
months ago. There's no sneaking.
I would have told you all of this,
but you're traveling so much,
I didn't want to do that
on a text message.
And I promise, this is not gonna affect
your marriage to Richard.
I'm not sure how much longer
you have to worry about that.
What's that supposed to mean?
Richard is working with someone
that he may or may not have
a romantic past with.
So, kind of like you and Koracick?
- That is different.
- How?
Because I don't have a history
of cheating on my spouse.
Oh, Mom. Come on.
Richard would lie down
in traffic for you,
- and you know it.
- I might ask him to.
Mom.
Sometimes, when you get
an idea in your head
that you don't like, you retreat.
I do it, too.
We've just...
barely spoken in weeks.
Have you barely spoken,
or you just don't want to listen?
If I've learned anything,
it's don't be a hero.
Use formula when you need formula.
Oh, trust me, I'm all over that.
Breast is best, but, sometimes,
Mommy needs wine.
Okay, one more deep breath for me.
Okay. We're ready to prep you, Elliott.
- Okay.
- Uh-huh.
I'm gonna go watch bad TV
and eat pudding and ice my lady parts.
Ooh-la-la.
Enjoy it, 'cause it's
gonna be your last alone time
for the next 18 years.
I don't have to be scared, right?
If I die, don't ever leave him
with my mother for the weekend.
Shut up.
And I won't.
We're gonna fix you up so you
can hold that beautiful boy.
- Hey.
- Huh?
Not my usual spot for a meeting,
but this will do.
How are you feeling, really?
Well, between losing Sabrina
and things with Catherine, um...
I don't know.
Loss is hard enough
without suffering it alone.
When my husband died, I was...
I didn't know you were ever married.
Oh, I don't talk about it that much.
We married young.
He died young.
I was a widow young.
That's when I started to drink.
Come on. Let's pray.
Okay.
Hi, Dr. Webber.
Um, Dr. Roth paged me
to do a Dobhoff tube,
but I have a very serious gag reflex,
- so I was wondering...
- Um, just do your job, Perez.
Got it. Thank you, sir.
Nice to meet you, Mrs. Webber.
Oh.
Come on, now.
God...
...grant me the serenity...
to accept the things I cannot change.
Hey. Hi.
Hey.
Do you need anything?
Oh, uh, no.
Um, Ben is grabbing a bottle
for him, so I just...
God, I don't know.
This is just so surreal.
Yeah. Yeah, babies freak me out, too.
Oh, no. Um, this... this baby is me.
I was, uh, abandoned
at a fire station by my mom
when I was 5 days old.
Right. So, you know, it's...
seems perfectly natural and healthy
that you would volunteer for this, then.
What?
Well, it made sense at the time.
So, you grew up in the system?
Yeah.
Me too.
Huh.
Did you have any good parents?
All crap.
You?
I had one good family.
It only lasted about a year, though.
But now I got these fools,
so all of it worked out in the end.
So, um... how often does this happen?
We only get like seven a year.
In the whole city.
Only seven abandoned babies?
Wow. What a freaking blessing.
We don't like to use
the word "abandoned."
I mean, they're, uh, they're surrendered.
By people who decided
they weren't fit to parent.
We try not to judge.
But sometimes, we do.
Look, Jo, you know...
no one's ever happy
about surrendering a baby,
but at least they know that
we'll keep the baby safe.
Hey, you, uh... you want to feed him?
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Oh, my gosh. Wow. Look at you.
You can't hate me forever.
I know I screwed all of us
by getting Meredith Grey fired,
but I was just trying not
to get myself fired.
I made a mistake,
and I thought you, of all
people, would understand that.
Why me of all people?
Because you mess up, too.
You're just better
at covering your ass than I am.
Hey, guys?
Uh, if I don't make it
through this surgery,
I'm gonna be really bummed
if this fight of yours
is the last thing I hear.
Sorry.
Actually, can we make a stop?
Oh, God.
Hey.
I just wanted to see him
before I went under...
just in case.
Elliott.
Ahhhh.
Go get a cow valve already, will you?
Moo.
I love you guys.
Okay, page me the second
Path has results.
- Hey.
Ohh. I think my
morning sickness has passed.
Ah. My morning sickness
came in the afternoon.
- Mm.
- Glad that's over.
I'm having the ultrasound
later today, but I'm torn.
A-Are you gonna find out the sex?
Nah.
I never understood
the whole gender reveal thing.
I mean, as if you could know
a kid's gender
from a blood test.
Well, you can.
You can know the sex, not the gender.
Gender is more than just pink
or blue icing in a sheet cake.
Hmm.
You know, in some cultures,
they recognize
as many as six different genders.
Right. So, on your last ultrasound,
you opted not to find out.
I, uh, actually haven't had one yet.
How many weeks are you?
Mm... 20?
Amelia Shepherd.
You're a doctor.
I know. I should have had one already.
I just am...
...terrified of what I might find out.
I just can't stop thinking, "What if?"
What if it happens again,
or w-what if it's something worse?
What if it's an alien? Or a tumor?
What if I am not even pregnant,
I am just a crazy person,
and I just exploded my boyfriend's life
for no reason?
The best way to fight fear
is with information.
You can't fix what you don't know.
Pregnancy Club just got way less fun.
Laurie Reed, return to the admit desk.
I checked with the mail room.
- No packages for you.
- Thanks.
Didn't realize the residents
were also our personal assistants.
I was doing Dr. Grey a favor.
Well, Grey, if you've got errands to run,
I've got this covered.
Look at that.
Mass between the 9th and 10th ribs.
That's easily accessible.
Simms, book an OR.
Make sure the lab's ready
to run the biopsy.
But it may not be a tumor.
Well, maybe you haven't
seen many sarcomas.
I've seen everything, thanks.
And I did take out
her gallbladder two years ago,
so some gallstones may have spilled
and migrated to her back.
So, your medical opinion is
you did shoddy work?
My medical opinion is
I see no need to worry her mother
with talk of tumors or cancer
unless we really need to.
Who are you, exactly?
Meredith Grey.
I'm chief of general surgery.
Oh, Grey. Yeah.
I've heard of you.
You're the one who got yourself
and half the staff fired, yeah?
Who hired you? Bailey or Koracick?
Why?
Bailey usually has too much
sense to hire surgeons
whose egos are too big to fit in an OR.
Let's prep her for a core needle biopsy,
and don't say a thing
to her mother about cancer.
Hey, uh, you want a ride to the hospital?
Miranda's got an ultrasound,
so I'm taking the afternoon off.
How can a person do this?
I mean, I-I-I thought I would
do this volunteer thing
and understand better,
and maybe I could forgive my mother.
But I can't.
I-I... I can't call what she did brave.
I-I can't call it "surrendering."
I...
And just looking...
at this tiny, little guy,
I understand even less
how she did what she did.
- Jo, just as a reminder...
- Yeah.
...trauma and... and your brain chemicals
c-can prompt a human being
to behave in ways
that people with more
balanced brain chemistry
can have a hard time understanding.
Right.
Link thinks this is too much too soon.
Let's get this guy to the hospital.
You can hand him off
to the social worker there.
We did his physical exam,
and he is all good.
Yeah.
Except for the fact that
his parents don't want him.
No, the people who gave birth
to him don't want him.
His parents...
just haven't met him yet.
Okay.
What's the activated clotting time?
485 seconds.
Thank you.
You asked that three minutes ago.
I know. DeBakey and 15 blade.
I was visiting Owen
at Pac North the other day.
Whew! Karev has his work cut out for him.
Mm-hmm. We've got a good plane
between the calcified
and the normal tissue.
Owen's been begging me
to come over there,
fix the cardio department.
Apparently, their top surgeon
is, like, 200th in the country.
I mean, i-it might be a good
opportunity to build a program.
Time to separate the valve
from the annulus.
I mean, I'm happy in trauma for now,
and you are doing a terrific job here,
but, God, do I miss this.
Dr. Altman, I asked you to scrub in today
to help speed things along,
not chit-chat.
If you want to go work at Pac
North, go work at Pac North.
Metz.
God.
You.
Where is Dr. Webber's office?
Um, is he expecting you?
What is your name?
Z... Zander Perez.
Have you heard
of the Catherine Fox Foundation,
Zander Perez?
No.
Well, I am Catherine Fox.
I own the foundation,
and the foundation owns 30%
of all the hospitals in America.
Oh.
Does it own this one?
Just show me to his office, son.
Okay. Of course.
But, actually, can you wait right here
while I page Dr. Webber?
He was having coffee with his wife,
so I don't want to interrupt them.
I am his wife.
Oh.
My.
Um...
What are you talking about?
I can't believe...
Parker!
I couldn't stop him.
Mommy, you said I wasn't dying.
Okay, honey, stay calm. You're not dying.
I want you to have all
the information as we have it.
No more surprises than
are absolutely necessary.
Dr. Grey. So, I know this is scary,
but Jamie has not exhibited any symptoms
that would prompt us to believe
this is a worst-case scenario.
So, let's not try to go there.
We'll know more in a few hours.
Mommy, I'm scared.
I know, honey. Me too.
We'll bring her up to the OR shortly.
Is this what you wanted?
This has got nothing to do
with what I want.
Am I a terrible mother and a worse doctor
for not getting an ultrasound?
You haven't gotten an ultrasound?
Okay.
Your question kind of
answers my question.
I just...
You're halfway through the pregnancy.
Don't we want to know
everything there is to know?
He dumped my sister,
and you put him on your service?
Unreal. That...
I did not dump her.
You didn't?
No.
You want to go clear that up?
She doesn't see me as her equal,
so I told her to take some time and...
figure out what she wants.
What?
I... I want to be supportive
because I can see you're upset,
but, uh... I'm confused.
And she doesn't see you
as her equal 'cause...
you're not her equal.
I mean, no offense. Neither am I.
I'm great. She's... better.
And you're...
still a resident.
It's just a matter of respect.
Yeah, well, my boyfriend isn't my equal.
Doesn't mean I don't respect him.
But if he told me to "take some time"...
Yeah, no, I would not respect that.
Dude...
go get her and undo
whatever it is you did,
because you're not her equal,
but she fell in love with you
knowing the facts.
But when you try to make
the facts not the facts,
that's how you drive someone crazy.
Valve's in, and we're
almost done closing the aorta.
Okay.
Okay, good. Good.
- Nice work, Pierce.
- Thank you.
Always heard you were
even better with hearts
than with bloody guts.
Didn't believe it could be true, Altman,
but you proved me wrong.
Thank you, Tom.
Why don't you just tell him
to leave you alone?
He's my boss.
And I broke his heart, and I feel guilty.
Wow. So many lawsuits in one explanation.
He's fine. He's harmless.
And we're friends.
Does he know that?
'Cause he seems to think
that he has a future with you,
and you don't seem to be
interested in clearing that up.
Okay. Clamps off.
Let's take the patient off bypass.
Dr. Altman, they need you in the pit.
You're good to close, yeah?
Yes. Thank you for the assist.
Mm-hmm.
Dr. Pierce? Uh, since I was the one
who was supposed to be
on your service today,
do you think I could close?
Dr. Pierce?
Shut up. Shut up. Um...
Shouldn't his heart be restarting by now?
I don't know why...
why it isn't restarting.
Why isn't it restarting?
What is it?
Lymphoma?
I thought I was out of the woods.
Listen, uh, the good news is
treatment options
are fairly straightforward.
I'm not doing chemo.
Chemo made me sicker
than cancer ever could.
Okay, Pruitt, testicular lymphoma
is extremely aggressive.
We're talking less than six months
before it gets to the lungs.
Dr. Bailey, you're bleeding.
Thank you again for today.
You want me to wait until
the social worker shows up?
No. I'm good.
Oh, no. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I got to...
Charge to 30.
Come on, Elliott. Come on.
Clear.
God. This can't be happening.
This can't be happening again!
Should we try e-epi and milrinone?
We've already dosed him twice.
Increase the flow on the pump.
You're just gonna keep him on bypass?
Helm, I said shut up.
What the hell happened?
- Pierce?
- His heart didn't restart.
I don't know what I did.
He's been on bypass
multiple times before, right?
It's probably hibernating myocardium.
Let's keep him up here
for a couple hours.
It could come back.
Pierce, do you agree
with my recommendation?
Pierce.
Well, I'm not gonna...
I'm not gonna go out there
and tell his wife and newborn
that he's dead,
so I guess I don't have a choice.
Pack the chest. Keep him on bypass.
I'm gonna scrub in.
You're just gonna have to wait now.
What happened?
Miranda?
Outside if you need me.
I'm so sorry.
Dr. Grey, we have
an update on that package
- you were looking for.
- Great.
They haven't found it yet.
Any word from the lab?
How's that core biopsy?
Pathology's saying they're just seeing
inflammatory cells
and cholesterol deposits.
No malignancy at all?
- No.
- Okay. Scalpel.
What are you doing?
I'm gonna take this whole thing out,
and see what the hell it is.
Dr. Grey, I didn't okay this.
Listen, Dr. Whoever You Are,
this is my house.
You're a guest in my home.
I got this.
Bovie.
So, what do you think?
Should I call Seattle Pres and gloat?
I don't know.
Pools of blood notwithstanding,
you are pretty impressive.
I got some options to consider.
Well, please think about it.
Okay.
Okay. What?
Just be careful.
Take it from me...
that's a slippery slope.
I'm not dead inside, okay?
And I'm very happily taken.
Oh. Did you propose to Teddy?
Not yet, but I...
But what? Waiting for her
to have your third child?
Dr. Vizant to the cath lab.
Looks like some inflamed tissue.
Can I get some light, please?
Oh, my God.
Parker, what are we looking at?
It looks like...
is that a large gallstone?
It's a large gallstone.
In the posterior chest wall?
Her body reacted to it
like it was foreign tissue
and tried to push it out.
Oh, I'm sorry. Do I sound smug?
You saw that from a scan?
Okay. Let's get some irrigation
and some 2-0 vicryl,
close her up, and get her home.
I'll take a veggie burger and
fries, please.
You are late.
What's that?
Uh, gin and... tonic.
Bring us three more.
It's true.
Richard is having an affair.
- How do you know that?
- I saw him.
He had her in his office.
You saw Richard having sex
with somebody in his office?
The door was closed,
but the intern called her his wife.
We used to have sex
all the time in his office.
I don't need... That's...
Okay, look, that sounds like
a miscommunication to me.
Stop defending that man.
That man? Mom, we're
talking about Richard.
Yes, Richard... who turned his back on me
the minute he hit a little career bump.
You fired him.
I did no such thing.
Bailey fired him.
You could have saved his job,
and you know that.
How dare you accuse me
of not supporting my husband,
when you got another little girlfriend
before Maggie's body's even cold.
How is that relevant
or any of your business?
It's my business
when you chose to date
my husband's daughter.
Where are those drinks?!
Mom, please, okay?
I cannot be responsible
for my relationships
and yours, all right?
There's not enough therapy
in the damn world for that.
Tip him.
Dr. James to respiratory therapy.
Miranda.
Uh, I'm fine.
- Let me take you home.
- No.
- Come on, Miranda.
- Oh, Ben. Please.
Um... I-I know... I know this
is a-a loss for you, too,
but I'm asking you to just
leave me alone f-for now,
because I can't... I can't feel this now.
I need to change these clothes,
and... and, uh, go to work,
so you need to leave.
Go d-drink with your buddies,
or... or throw things.
Anything but being... here,
looking at me,
with those sad, beautiful eyes.
Hey!
Did you get that ultrasound?
Yes.
Uh, and you should, too.
It's important.
I'm gonna go tonight.
Good.
Did you decide
if you wanted to know the sex?
Yeah. It's a... It's a girl.
Girl!
I don't think I understand.
Does he need a new valve?
He just...
needs more time.
Okay.
How much time?
Well, we can't be sure.
With hibernating myocardium,
the odds of his heart restarting
are very high.
We just don't know how long it'll take.
Wait. You're saying...
...it might not start at all?
There is a very small chance, but...
No, this has to be a mistake.
He's had this surgery three times before.
You've done it three times before.
Yes. I have.
Then, what happened?
I-I... I don't know, Finley.
Oh, my God.
- I'm sorry.
- Oh, my God.
Will you please... Will you excuse me?
Pierce.
W-What happened in that OR?
I would like to tender my resignation...
- effective immediately.
- No, no, h-hang on.
One bad outcome is not...
I had a bad feeling. I know that patient.
I had a bad feeling.
I should have trusted myself.
I can't be a surgeon
if I can't trust my own gut.
I can't.
I quit.
Y...
I seem to be in need of a cardio chief.
- Interested?
- What?
Tom, you can't just fire people
to give me what you think I need.
I have... I have moved on.
I love Owen.
I am sorry that I hurt you.
I mean, truly sorry.
You... You are a wonderful man,
and you are gonna make some woman...
or several women... incredibly happy.
But, uh, you have just...
you have got to stop barking
up this particular tree.
I-I didn't fire Pierce.
She quit.
Oh. Oh.
But I do think you should be
my cardio chief.
- Okay.
- And, Teddy?
Mm-hmm?
I want a life with you.
I'd marry you tomorrow,
right now, if you said yes.
Owen has a baby with you,
and he hasn't proposed.
Are you really sure you want to...
close this door?
Well, thank you. Thank you so much.
This has been hell.
I can only imagine.
But this is good news, Jamie.
You're going to get to go to
your dance zit-hump free.
It doesn't matter.
Zachary still hasn't texted me back.
Oh.
What age is this boy? Zachary?
13. My age.
Well, as someone who's raised
a couple of 13-year-old boys,
I can tell you two things...
first is, the only
thoughts in their heads
are "Fortnite" and pizza.
And the second is,
they're terrified of girls,
can't talk to them...
especially the ones they like.
Ah.
Catherine's gonna be out of town.
I didn't even know she was in town.
She's thinks there's
something going on between us,
doesn't she?
Yes.
- Hey.
How'd it go? How you doing?
Thanks for coming over.
Uh-oh.
Was I right?
Was it too much too soon?
Do we need vodka?
One could argue that it was,
in fact, too much too soon.
Home means different
things to different people.
Sometimes, home is a person.
_
So, is your thing
to terrify them for no reason
and then bask in the relief?
I'm not interested in trying to guess
what people want to hear.
I prefer to give them all the information
and let them figure out
how to deal with it.
My wife's doctors didn't pay me
that respect before she died.
Listen, Grey, this is your house,
but someone gave me a key,
so maybe it's best if we...
try to learn how to live together.
Welcome back, Dr. Grey.
_
I can see why you were missed.
Home can be a feeling.
Psychiatrists say,
for those of us who come from
dysfunctional homes...
Everything's fine?
Perfectly fine.
...that feeling is chaos.
But...
uh, you're not 20 weeks pregnant.
I'm not?
No. Y-You're 24.
No. That's not possible.
No? No.
Because that could mean...
Oh, God.
No.
We think family means drama.
They were awful all day long.
And you promised me a reward.
Food first, then dessert.
I disagree with that order.
My wife miscarried
before Andrea was born.
It's painfully common.
Captain Herrera...
Got it. Shutting up.
Why were you at the hospital?
So is no wonder why so many of us
from broken homes
Drives on pain and destruction.
www.tvsubtitles.net